The Day You Went Away
Artist M2M
HIM
Well I wonder could it be
When I was dreaming
about you baby
You were dreaming of me
Call me crazy,Call me blind
To still be suffering is
stupid after all of this time
Did I lose my love
to someone better
And does she love you like I do
I do, you know I
really really do
Well hey,So much I need to say
Been lonely since the day
The day you went away
So sad but true
For me there's only you
Been crying since the day
the day you went away
I remember date and time
September twenty second
Sunday twenty five after nine
In the doorway with your case
No longer shouting
at each other
There were tears on our faces
And we were letting go
of something special
Something we'll
never have again
I know, I guess I
really really know
Well hey,So much I need to say
Been lonely since the day
The day you went away
So sad but true
For me there's only you
Been crying since the day
the day you went away
Did I lose my love
to someone better
And does she love you like I do
I do, you know I
really really do
Well hey,So much I need to say
Been lonely since the day
The day you went away
So sad but true
For me there's only you
Been crying since the day
the day you went away
Why do we never know what
we've got till it's gone
How could I carry on
the day you went away
Cause I've been missing
you so much I have to say
Been crying since the day
the day you went away