You get up every morning,
From your alarm
clock's warning,
Take the 8:15 into the city.
There's a whistle up above,
And people pushin',
people shovin',
And the girls who
try to look pretty.
And if your train's on time,
You can get to work by nine,
And start your slavin'
job to get your pay.
If you ever get annoyed,
Look at me I'm self-employed.
I love to work at
nothing all day.
And I'll be Takin' Care
Of Business, every day!
Takin' Care Of
Business, every way!
I've been Takin' Care Of
Business, it's all mine!
Takin' Care Of Business
and working overtime!
Work out!
If it were easy as fishin',
You could be a musician,
If you could make
sounds loud or mellow.
Get a second-hand guitar.
Chances are you'll go far,
If you get in with the
right bunch of fellows.
People see you having fun,
Just a-lying in the sun.
Tell them that you
like it this way.
It's the work that we avoid.
And we're all self-employed.
We love to work at
nothing all day.
And we've been Takin' Care
Of Business, every day!
Takin' Care Of
Business, every way!
We've been Takin' Care Of
Business, it's all mine!
Takin' Care Of Business
and working overtime!
Take good care of my business.
When I'm away, every day!
Wooo!
You get up every morning,
From your alarm
clock's warning,
Take the 8:15 into the city.
There's a whistle up above,
And people pushin',
people shovin',
And the girls who
try to look pretty.
And if your train's on time,
You can get to work by nine,
And start your slavin'
job to get your pay.
If you ever get annoyed,
Look at me I'm self-employed.
I love to work at
nothing all day.
And I'll be Takin' Care
Of Business, every day!
Takin' Care Of
Business, every way!
I've been Takin' Care Of
Business, it's all mine!
Takin' Care Of Business
and working overtime!
Takin' Care Of Business.
Takin' Care Of
Business, every day!
Business, every way!
Takin' Care Of
Business, it's all mine!
Takin' Care Of Business
and working overtime!
Takin' Care Of Business.
We've been Takin'
Care Of Business.
Takin' Care Of Business.